

## **ANDREY PAVLYCHEV**

**2D/UI ARTIST** 

ADDRESS: Nha Trang, Vietnam PHONE: +84 (093) 595-07-69

E-MAIL: drawn.loves.you@gmail.com

WEB: http:///drawn.pro, https://dribbble.com/drawn

# **PROFILE**

2D and User Interface artist with about 10 years experience in artwork production for mobile and social network games. I specialize in user interfaces, icon and application design. As for my competency, I have strong knowledge of Adobe Creative Suite, 2D digital drawing skills with use of Photoshop, Illustrator and Flash. Experienced in all phases of UI development, visual and technical, starting from concept up to the final design.

Being a flexible artist, I can work in a team or figure out solutions individually as well. Self-motivated and organized, able to work within established style and tight deadlines. Passionate about iconography and vector graphics.

## **EXPERIENCE**

### **FREELANCE ARTIST**

Thailand, Vietnam | January 2015 - Present

Projects include game assets, icons, app design, UI and logo design.

### **UI DESIGNER**

KRIVORUKOFF LLP | Samui, Thailand | March 2014 — January 2015

Worked on mobile games being in charge for:

- UI restyling
- UI/UX elements wireframing, design and implementation (Unity3D NGUI Framework)
- · Animated UI pre-vis
- Icon design

Projects: Adventure Era, Unannounced project.

### **2D ARTIST AND ANIMATOR**

CRAZYBIT LLC | Moscow, Russia | July 2010 — March 2014

Browser, Social and Mobile game assets development. Duties included:

- · UI design and animation
- Sprite animations sequences
- · Flash animation
- · Character skeletal animation
- Wide variety of icons (Item icons, ability icons, UI icons, app icons etc)
- · Logo design
- · Promotional materials

Projects: Lost Island, Lost Chapters, Island Experiment, Supernova, Hellout, WarDogs, Soldiers of Fortune, S.O.S, Metro City, Sinners, BOOM!

### **FLASH DESIGNER**

 ${\tt IT-TERRITORY/ASTRUM-ONLINE/MAIL.RU\mid Moscow, Russia\mid December\ 2009-July\ 2010-Line (Mail.)}$ 

Worked on several game projects in a mixture of roles including:

- UI design/restyling
- UI animation
- · Icon design
- In game items design
- Character Animation

Projects: TimeZero, Juggernaut, Legends: Legacy of the Dragons, Urban Fight, Cosmics: Galactic Wars, Troetsarstvie.

### **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

TIMEZERO LLC | Moscow, Russia | September 2007 — December 2009

Worked on a wide range of projects, from browser MMORPGs to amazing casual Flash games under Facebook and Vkontakte. Was in charge for:

- · Graphic design
- · UI design
- · Icon design
- · 2D animations for characters and FX
- · Character gear set design
- · In game items design
- · Flash banners
- · Promotional materials
- · Merchandise products design

Projects: TimeZero, Destiny Online, BUGS, Evil Tale, Crouching Panda Hidden Moose, Funny War, Dragons, Pyramid.

### **DESIGNER**

ERA LLC | Moscow, Russia | October 2006 — August 2007

Transformed company's website to deliver more appealing interface. Managed content. Designed packaging and promotional materials.

# **EDUCATION**

Saransk, Russia | 2002 — 2008

Area Studies Specialist, Mordovia State University

Saransk, Russia | 1996 - 2001

Pictural Art Department, Saransk State Art School #4

# **SKILLS**

User Interface design, Interaction design, Wireframes, Icon Design, Game items design, Logo Design, UI and Character animation (2D), Flash and GIF banners

# **SOFTWARE**

Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, Flash, Sketch app, Unity3D. Some experience with Adobe After Effects, HTML, CSS. JIRA, Redmine, Trello, GitHub. OSX